

# HANA HUMAIRA Public Relation Manager

Kebon Jeruk, West Jakarta

082298635951

**▼** Humairahana 19@gmail.com

# **Software Skills**

Microsft Word	ı	_	<b>75</b> %
Microsft Excel	I		70%
Microsft Powerpoint		_	65%
Photoshop	1	_	80%

# **Social**

Facebook humaira.hana@facebook

Twitter humaira.hana@twitter

Humaira\_Hana

# Objective

Ho, my name is Hana Humaira I'm twenty-nine years old, single and In good health. I have my bachelor degree from London School Of Public Relations who are enthusiastic internet believers; good team work skill, good building relationships, capable to perform in the highest achievement for exclent results and seeking for a challenging career opportunity. I have 4 years experience of working as a Public Relations, and I'm ready to work for your companyl why dont we work together? go further down to see why I'm the girl you need to hire!

# Work Experience

#### 2020-2021

Garuda Indonesia
I worked as Pisultant & Media Relation

#### 2013-2020

Garuda Indonesia I worked as Public Relations Manage

# 2015-2018

Bank Mandiri Google Indonesia I worked as Public Relations Manager

#### Education

#### 2007-2011

SMP N 134 Jakarta

#### 2011-2013

SMA N 112 Jakarta

#### 2013-2015

**London School Of Public Relations** 

# Things I Enjoy







